equator.com 2011-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Equator, LLC

  * Home
  *  » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

EQUATOR FINANCIAL SOLUTIONS

PRIVACY STATEMENT

This notice details the privacy policies of Equator Financial Solutions for consumers, realtors and real estate agents accessing its website located at www.equator.com, including how Equator Financial Solutions protects information provided or collected through this website. Questions regarding this statement should be directed by e-mail to agenthelp@equator.com. You may also contact us at Equator Financial Solutions, Privacy Division, located at 6060 Center Drive, Suite 500, Los Angeles, California 90045. 

What information does Equator collect and how does Equator use it?  

Consumers - You may visit and use certain features of our website without any registration, in which case none of your personal information will be collected or retained. However for you to register and take advantage of the benefits and exclusive features of the Equator website, you are required to provide your name, email address, home address and phone number, a password, and whether you are a first time home buyer, investor or an existing home owner. We may additionally request you to provide your business name, address, phone number and fax number and various demographic information about yourself on an optional basis.

Agents - You may visit and use certain features of our website without any registration, in which case none of your personal information will be collected or retained. However for you to register and take advantage of the benefits and exclusive features of the Equator website, you are required to provide your name, email address, real estate license number and issuing state, a password for your account and business address and phone number. You may additionally add your mobile phone number, business name and facsimile number and home address, phone number and facsimile number. In addition, by registering through the website, you expressly authorize Equator to create a performance profile about you as an agent including statistical information with respect to your response times and sales statistics. This profile will solely be accessible to lenders accessing the website.  

This allows us to properly and effectively integrate you into the website database in order to provide you with the functionality, feedback, support and any information you request. We may additionally use the information we collect to occasionally seek feedback from you regarding potential Equator products and services and to notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new products and services available through the website or otherwise offered by Equator, and special offers we think you’ll find valuable.  

We may additionally use information provided through our website and services to compile performance and analysis reports pertaining to agents, vendors and other users of our website and systems. We may additionally collect website data to contact any entities who access or use our website unless the entity “opts-out” from being contacted. You may choose to opt-out from being contacted by removing your information from our databases as provided in this Privacy Statement.  

Notwithstanding any other term of this Privacy Policy, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.  

**How does Equator protect visitor information?**  
Equator uses industry-standard technologies when storing, transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged to help ensure its security. This includes password protected member records, firewalls, secure servers and SSL encryption.  

**Does Equator use “cookies”?**  
Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. We currently save preference information in cookies. Though most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent the storage of any cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie.  

**Does Equator disclose any personally identifiable information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?**  
Equator may transfer, sell and otherwise may share the information you provide to us to select partners and third parties. This will allow these third parties to contact you and provide you offers and other information that they think will be valuable to you. However, if you would like Equator to stop providing your information to these third parties, please log into your account through the Equator website and change your account settings to opt-out of being contacted by third parties.

Equator, and any of its affiliates or contractors, may (a) use, sell or transfer any anonymous aggregated statistical user data in any manner, at any time and (b) freely transfer any and all information you provide us to any of our subsidiary, parent and/or affiliate companies.  

**Equator’s special note to parents**  
In compliance with the 1998 Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Equator is a general audience website, and does not knowingly collect, nor will ever knowingly retain, personally identifiable information from any visitor Equator actually knows to be under thirteen years of age without the consent of that child’s parent or legal guardian.  

**How does a visitor remove or modify the information they have provided to Equator?**  
After gathering any user information, Equator offers users the opportunity to remove their information from our database so as not to receive future communications or to no longer interact with the website until they later chose to by logging into your account through the Equator website and changing your account settings and preferences. However, once removed from Equator’s database, users will no longer be able to access any of the exclusive features offered to registered users.  

**Third party links and co-brand relationships**  
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, Equator may choose various third party websites to link to and from, and frame within, its own website. Equator may also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer information, programs and other services and features to its users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with Equator, Equator has no control over these linked sites, and each of these sites has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of Equator. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such websites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Accordingly, please carefully review the data collection policies on each of these websites.  

**Your consent, policy changes and change of ownership**  
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Equator as set forth in this Privacy Statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what limited circumstances we disclose it. Continued access or use of the website shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this Privacy Statement. In the event that Equator or a substantial portion of Equator’s assets are acquired, customer information collected and retained in accordance with this Privacy Statement may be one of the transferred assets.  

Legal Disclaimer:  
By using the website, you irrevocably acknowledge and agree that Equator merely provides technological tools that vendors, brokers, agents, buyers, sellers and other individuals and/or companies may use to transact business. Equator is not involved in the actual transaction between buyers, agents, brokers, lenders, sellers and any other related party, and is not the agent of, nor has any authority on behalf of any of the aforementioned parties or any other third party, for any purpose whatsoever. At no time and in no event shall Equator become involved in any dispute or transaction between the aforementioned parties or have any responsibility or liability in connection therewith, including, but not limited to, making or guaranteeing any payment that may come due as a result of any transaction or agreement between the aforementioned parties.

 Additional Information Questions regarding this policy or the practices of Equator should be directed to Equator at agenthelp@equator.com. You may also contact us at Equator Financial Solutions, Privacy Division, located at 6060 Center Drive, Suite 500, Los Angeles, California 90045.
